Date of birth: 08 September 1988

Citizenship: Ukrainian

Address: 10/5 Worcella Street, 50-448, Wroclaw, Poland

Telephone: +48 794 924 297 Email: olga_morgunova@ukr.net

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/OlgaMorgunova



SUMMARY

An ambitious and skilled professional with five years of relevant experience and knowledge in financial analysis, business valuation, performing financial and operational audits of processes and controls, SOX audit engagements.

Seeking for a challenging position within a company in Financial Analysis or Controlling, that will allow me to display my experience, good problem solving skills and analytical mind to contribute to a company's growth. Looking forward to using my skills for the betterment of the company and improvement of my potential as well.

Address: 10/5 Worcella Street, 50-448, Wroclaw, Poland

Telephone: +48 794 924 297 Email: olga_morgunova@ukr.net

WORK EXPERIENCE

Job Title: Internal Audit Analyst Company: Hewlett Packard Enterprise

Feb. 2015 – to present Wroclaw, Poland

Activities/Achievements:

- As Internal Auditor I am engaged in performing audit and assurance activities for a variety of financial, operational and IT processes and controls, based on experience ability and departmental needs.
- Apply developed subject matter knowledge to solve common and complex business issues within established guidelines and recommend appropriate alternatives.
- Act as team member by providing information, analysis and recommendations in support of team efforts.
- Work on problems of diverse complexity and scope.
- Exercise independent judgment within generally defined policies and practices to identify and select a solution. Ability to handle most unique situations.
- Knowledgeable in Sarbanes-Oxley.

Responsibilities

- Audit complex business processes and perform ad-hoc internal audits.
- Identify inherent and residual risks and conducts risk-based audits.
- Develops an in-depth understanding of the function to be audited, summarize findings and identify improvements.
- Supervise assigned audit activities.
- Conduct complex research and data analysis for various audit projects.
- Stay abreast of leading practices in auditing procedures, accounting regulations, governmental regulations, and internal control procedures.

Job Title: Senior Auditor Company: KPMG Ukraine Oct. 2011 – Jan. 2015 Kyiv, Ukraine

Activities/Achievements:

- Led audits of consolidated financial statements of major Ukrainian companies prepared in accordance with IFRS in diverse industries such as dairy and whole-milk, spirits and beverages, agriculture producers among many others. Led audits of stand-alone financial statements prepared in accordance with IFRS and NAS.
- Set up goals, budget, and fieldwork monitoring to manage projects. Led the formulation and delivery of
 risk-based audit plans, influencing the client's business strategy and policy, working practices and
 standards by providing insight, control and thought leadership. Conducted risk analysis procedures and
 presented findings as well as recommendations to top management. Supervised audit teams, ensuring
 adequate working papers and providing coaching where appropriate to support performance and
 individuals to deliver on their potential (teams of 2 to 4 auditors).
- Prepared transformations of financial statements from local NAS to IFRS; prepared tax and deferred tax computations.
- Prepared Discounted Cash Flow (DCF) models for business valuation purposes.

Olga Morgunova

Email: olga_morgunova@ukr.net Page 1

Address: 10/5 Worcella Street, 50-448, Wroclaw, Poland

Telephone: +48 794 924 297 Email: olga_morgunova@ukr.net

• Identified and presented reporting issues to management. Prepared drafts for final documents and reports to be reviewed by senior managers and partners.

- Compiled and presented audit findings. Reported on the weaknesses within the customer's accounting
 documentation and internal control systems. Solid controls and best practice business improvements were
 given to the client.
- Rated as «Highly Effective Performance» within the KPMG's Performance Development (MyPD).

Auditing experience in the following industries (including first-year clients):

- FMCG (dairy and whole-milk products; spirits and beverage).
- Agricultural industry (crops; livestock; grain elevator services).
- Technology (software outsourcing, telecommunication).
- Coal mining, power transmission and distribution networks and many others

Job Title: International Sales Representative

Company: UFC Capital, LLC

Aug. 2010 – Sept. 2011 Kyiv, Ukraine

Activities/Achievements:

- Engaged in trading Eurobonds of CIS countries and Ukrainian VAT Bonds with customers in Europe, USA, Russia and China. Used Bloomberg trading system.
- Maintained and developed existing client base; transactions support.

EDUCATION, HONORS AND CERTICATES

Accounting Certificates

Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (10 papers passed).

December 2011 to present

Master's Degree in Finance (M.A.) GPA 4.5 out of 5

University: Vadim Getman Kyiv National University of Economics

2009-2010 Kyiv, Ukraine

Awarded full tuition, merit-based fellowship for outstanding academic achievements

Bachelor's Degree in Finance

2005-2009

University: Vadim Getman Kyiv National University of Economics

Kyiv, Ukraine

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English Fluent verbal and written
- Ukrainian Mother Tongue
- Russian Mother Tongue
- Polish Elementary proficiency

Olga Morgunova

Email: olga_morgunova@ukr.net Page 2

Address: 10/5 Worcella Street, 50-448, Wroclaw, Poland

Telephone: +48 794 924 297 Email: olga_morgunova@ukr.net

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Internal audit, advisory and assurance, Sarbanes-Oxley Act, business and financial/operations analysis,
- Data management, corporate and financial reporting, auditing and accounting, IFRS, accounts reconciliation, project and team management, consulting, customer relationship management.

SOFT and COMPUTER SKILLS

- Strong computer knowledge in Microsoft Office Word, Excel, Power Point. Bloomberg trading computer system.
- In the process of learning VBA.
- Basic knowledge of 1C, Money and SAP accounting systems.
- Strong critical thinking and troubleshooting skills, analytical thinking.
- Ability to develop strong client and business relationships and demonstrate high levels of accountability and professionalism.
- Ability to work effectively both on a team and independently.
- Strong interpersonal and leadership skills. Ability to learn quickly.
- Self-discipline, punctuality, organization and responsibility.

INTERESTS and HOBBIES

- Volunteering helping a children hospice Fundacja Wrocławskie Hospicjum dla Dzieci (Wroclaw Poland), ARMIA SOS Ukraine – gathering clothes and food/medical supplies for Ukrainian military officers and soldiers in the East of Ukraine;
- Great fan of backgammon, squash and salsa dancing;

References and recommendations are available upon request.

Olga Morgunova @ukr p